<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>language on Call me Ben</title>
    <link>https://benfeifke.com/tags/language/</link>
    <description>Recent content in language on Call me Ben</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 09:47:45 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://benfeifke.com/tags/language/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>No, Neil Degrasse Tyson, Science isn&#39;t true whether or not I believe in it.</title>
      <link>https://benfeifke.com/posts/no-science-isnt-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 09:47:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benfeifke.com/posts/no-science-isnt-right/</guid>
      <description>Intro Back when Donald Trump got elected&amp;hellip;
list of quotes:
 degrasse tyson quote other quote  the problem is, they&amp;rsquo;re wrong
The Scientific Method when the sci
Where do we go from here? This isn&amp;rsquo;t to say all science is wrong. I&amp;rsquo;m simply trying to encourage a change in perspective.
Final Thoughts Science is expressive!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Two Documents you Must Prepare before beginning Data Science Interviews.</title>
      <link>https://benfeifke.com/posts/the-two-documents-every-data-scientist-must-prepare-before-interviewing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 09:47:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benfeifke.com/posts/the-two-documents-every-data-scientist-must-prepare-before-interviewing/</guid>
      <description>Intro I&amp;rsquo;ve given this advice to many people, thought I&amp;rsquo;d share.
Tell Me About Yourself Tell Me About A Project You&amp;rsquo;ve Worked On Final Thoughts </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why are the Most Common Verbs Irregular?</title>
      <link>https://benfeifke.com/posts/why-are-the-most-common-verbs-irregular-20220623/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 09:47:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benfeifke.com/posts/why-are-the-most-common-verbs-irregular-20220623/</guid>
      <description>Back when I was learning Portuguese, I often found myself wondering something that most language-learners probably wonder at some point: why the hell are there so many irregular verb conjugations in this language? And why are they so weird? It&amp;rsquo;s like someone purposefully designed this language to be hard to learn!
As it turns out, somebody didn&amp;rsquo;t design it to be that way. Rather, natural processes designed it so; processes that have been playing out over thousands of years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Denkmit</title>
      <link>https://benfeifke.com/posts/denkmit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 09:47:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benfeifke.com/posts/denkmit/</guid>
      <description>Denkmit One of the joys of learning a new language is discovering yourself in the language. Each new language is like a new color palette or musical instrument for self-expression. Everybody wields their language in a unique way; everybody has a unique voice. As I&amp;rsquo;ve begun to learn my next language (Hebrew), it&amp;rsquo;s time to retool. There are a lot of language-learning tools out there, but I was seeking something that would cater to my specific voice, and help me to pay closer attention where I needed to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Did We Count Before We Invented Numbers?</title>
      <link>https://benfeifke.com/posts/how-did-we-count-before-we-invented-numbers-20220624/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 09:47:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://benfeifke.com/posts/how-did-we-count-before-we-invented-numbers-20220624/</guid>
      <description>And Then There Were Numbers Sometimes, I like to imagine the moment that the Set of Natural Numbers was invented. It goes a little bit like this:
 Stage Left: Curt the Caveman walks in to Mack the Caveman&amp;rsquo;s cave; Mack is picking his teeth with a bone.
MACK: &amp;ldquo;Hey, Curt!&amp;rdquo;
CURT: &amp;ldquo;Mack! Great to see you. Beautiful day for tooth-pickin&amp;rsquo;, huh?&amp;rdquo;
MACK: &amp;ldquo;You bet, Curt. To what do I owe the pleasure of your visit?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
